Raymond Hui

Front-End Web Developer

Oakland, CA

(510) 846-7482

rwhui.tech@gmail.com

rhuitech.com

github.com/raywhui

in linkedin.com/in/raywhui/

Summary —

User-focused, full stack web developer with experience developing web and automation technologies at a rapidly-growing tech startup. Experienced in balancing multiple roles, working both independently and in a collaborative environment, and grasping new concepts and technologies quickly.

Technical Skills —

React.js APIs Firebase

Google Cloud Platform Node.js

AWS ES6 Git Shopify

WordPress phpMyAdmin SFTP

BigCommerce Salesforce

Libraries

Material UI Redux Bootstrap

Axios jQuery

Languages

JavaScript HTML5 CSS3

SQL Python Apex

Professional Experience –

Afterpay Touch

Software Engineer

Jun 2019 - Present

- Architected and developed a user interface redesign of an SMB Shopify Onboarding app to increase client self-installation rates.
- Integrated, QA tested, and deployed Afterpay functionality to merchant websites on various E-commerce platforms.
- Decreased dropped support inquiry rates by developing a merchant technical support form in Apex.
- Created crucial file conversion software that allowed high profile merchants to launch early.
- Frequently used various web services (AWS, Salesforce, RESTful APIs)

Side, Inc.

Implementation Engineer

Jun 2018 - May 2019

- Deployed and developed software for improved client onboarding.
- Developed a Material UI React component to automate DocuSign user creation, reducing time of setup from several minutes to seconds.
- Spearheaded the creation of a WordPress content automation tool, resulting in a 25% decrease in website development time.
- Contributed large improvements to the website template GitHub repository, decreasing the amount of manual tasks needed for website setup.
- Identified potential improvements to client onboarding and brainstormed solutions with colleagues across different departments.

Implementation Specialist

Apr 2018 - Jun 2018

- Implemented client systems and website setups/updates for over 70 unique accounts.
- Participated in both kanban and scrum methodologies involving sprint planning, daily standups, and retrospective.
- Demonstrated excellent autonomy and development skills, leading to a promotion and title change.

UC Berkeley Extension

Full Stack Instructional Aide

Nov 2018 - May 2019

- Responsible for fostering the web development skills of over 25 students.
- Enabled students to learn at a rapid pace through active communication.
- Enforced best coding practices through detailed documentation on student assignments.

Education ——

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development University of California, Berkeley Extension Jul 2017 - Jan 2018

B.Sc in Exercise Biology and Minor in Psychology *University of California, Davis*

Sep 2012 - Jul 2016